[{"answer": "How was your weekend", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " It was great.  How about yours", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 14, "question": "How was your weekend", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Mine was pretty good too.  Did you do anything special", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 15, "question": " It was great.  How about yours", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Kind of.  On Saturday, I spent the whole morning driving around to garag", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Mine was pretty good too.  Did you do anything special", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Garage sales?  What are those", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Kind of.  On Saturday, I spent the whole morning driving around to garag", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " You dont know what a garage sale is", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Garage sales?  What are those", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I dont think so.  Ive never heard of it before", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 22, "question": " You dont know what a garage sale is", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": "I guess they might just be popular in the U.S.  Here, when people have thing", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 23, "question": " I dont think so.  Ive never heard of it before", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Really?  What kind of things can you buy there", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 30, "question": "I guess they might just be popular in the U.S.  Here, when people have thing", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " Practically anything.  People sell clothing, furniture, toys, knickknacks", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Really?  What kind of things can you buy there", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": "Is it common for people to sell their own things here", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Practically anything.  People sell clothing, furniture, toys, knickknacks", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Well, when people are moving or cleaning out their houses, they often have ", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Is it common for people to sell their own things here", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Oh, OK.  Well, how do you know if someone is having a garage sale", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Well, when people are moving or cleaning out their houses, they often have ", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": "People put ads in the newspapers for the sales, so you can find out about the", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Oh, OK.  Well, how do you know if someone is having a garage sale", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " I think Ive seen one of those signs before.  I was wondering what that was.  Nex", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 46, "question": "People put ads in the newspapers for the sales, so you can find out about the", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": "There are some other things you should know about garage sales before goin", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 50, "question": " I think Ive seen one of those signs before.  I was wondering what that was.  Nex", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": "Like what", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 54, "question": "There are some other things you should know about garage sales before goin", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": "Well, you should always try to get the seller to lower their price on an item", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Like what", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Really?  But what would I say", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Well, you should always try to get the seller to lower their price on an item", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Say, for example, that you wanted to buy a shirt that cost $4.  You would sa", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Really?  But what would I say", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " OK.  I got it", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Say, for example, that you wanted to buy a shirt that cost $4.  You would sa", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Another thing to remember too is that you have to get to the sales early.  All o", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 65, "question": " OK.  I got it", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " What times are the sales usually", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Another thing to remember too is that you have to get to the sales early.  All o", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Usually theyre on Fridays and Saturdays and go from 7:00 or 8:00 in th", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 70, "question": " What times are the sales usually", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": "0 or 3:00 in the afternoon", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Usually theyre on Fridays and Saturdays and go from 7:00 or 8:00 in th", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Thats pretty early for shopping", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 73, "question": "0 or 3:00 in the afternoon", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " It is.  But, you have to be an early bird if you want to get the good stuff", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Thats pretty early for shopping", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": "Ill have to set my alarm early then", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 78, "question": " It is.  But, you have to be an early bird if you want to get the good stuff", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Itll be worth it if you find something great to buy.  I actually think its pretty fun", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Ill have to set my alarm early then", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " That does sound like fun", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Itll be worth it if you find something great to buy.  I actually think its pretty fun", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " You can come with me the next time I go if you want to check it out", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 85, "question": " That does sound like fun", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Sure.  That would be great", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 86, "question": " You can come with me the next time I go if you want to check it out", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Ill look in the paper at the end of this week and if I see any good sale ads, Il", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Sure.  That would be great", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK.  Thanks.  Ill be looking forward to my first garage sale", "docId": "07-08", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Ill look in the paper at the end of this week and if I see any good sale ads, Il", "qSentId": 90}]
